shoptalk.com 2017-10-02

# Privacy Policy — Shoptalk: the world’s largest conference for retail & commerce innovation

Shoptalk ("we" or "us") recognizes the importance of respecting the privacy of those who visit our website (our "Site"). We believe it is important for you to know how we treat the information about you that we receive during your visits to our Site. This Privacy Policy is designed to assist you in understanding how we collect, disclose, and safeguard various types of information, including the personally identifiable information you provide to us via our Site.

This Privacy Policy applies only to the information that we collect on our Site and not to any information that we collect through other methods or sources, including sites owned or operated by our affiliates, vendors, or partners. Please note that when you link from our Site to other websites, this Privacy Policy no longer applies.

You acknowledge that, by accessing or using our Site, you agree to be bound by all of the terms and conditions of use pertaining to our Site and contained in the Terms of Use (available at <http://shoptalk.com/page/terms>), including this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with this Privacy Policy, please do not access or use our Site.

We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time. Such changes, modifications, additions, or deletions shall be effective immediately upon posting thereof on our Site. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review our Site and this Privacy Policy periodically, and to be aware of any modifications. Your continued use of our Site after such modifications will constitute your: (a) acknowledgment of the modified Privacy Policy; and (b) agreement to abide and be bound by the modified Privacy Policy.

 **1\. Types of Information Collected**

We collect two types of information about our website users: Personally Identifiable Information and Non-Personally Identifiable Information. Our primary goal in collecting information from you is to provide you with a smooth, efficient, and customized experience while using our Site.

Personally Identifiable Information: this refers to information that lets us know the specifics of who you are. When you engage in certain activities on our Site, such as contacting us, registering for our mailing list, making a purchase or sending us feedback, we may ask you to provide certain information about yourself by filling out and submitting an online form. It is completely optional for you to engage in these activities; however, we may ask that you provide us personal information, such as your first and last name, mailing address (including zip code), e-mail address, employer, job title and department, telephone and facsimile numbers, and other personally identifying information. Depending upon your activity, some of the information we ask you to provide is identified as mandatory. If you do not provide the mandatory data with respect to a particular activity, you will not be able to engage in that activity.

Non-Personally Identifiable Information: this refers to information that does not by itself identify a specific individual. We gather certain information about you based upon where you visit on our Site in several ways. This information is compiled and analyzed on both a personal and an aggregated basis. This information may include the website's Uniform Resource Locator ("URL") that you just came from, which URL you next go to, what browser you are using, and/or your Internet Protocol ("IP") address.

 **2\. Collection Methods and Use of Information**

We do not collect any Personally Identifiable Information about you unless you voluntarily provide it to us. We will primarily use your Personally Identifiable Information to provide our services to you, as requested by you or as required by any agreements between us and you. We will also use Personally Identifiable Information to enhance the operation of our Site, fill improve our marketing and promotional efforts, statistically analyze site use, improve our product and service offerings, and customize our Site's content, layout, and services. We may use Personally Identifiable Information to deliver information to you and to contact you regarding administrative notices. We may also use Personally Identifiable Information to resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems, and enforce agreements with you, including this Privacy Policy.

In addition, we may also collect, or our third-party content server may collect, certain Non-Personally Identifiable Information. Our servers automatically collect certain site use information each time you visit our Site. The Site use information includes but is not limited to the following: the domain names, operating system in use, browser and version, the web site that referred you to us, and other similar information. This information may be aggregated to measure the number of visits, average time spent on our Site, pages viewed, time and date of visits, and other similar information. We may use and disclose site use information, for example, to measure the use of our Site, explain the utility of our Site, and to improve the content of our Site.

We also make use of "cookies" on our Site. A cookie is a small piece of data that our Site can send to your browser, which may then be stored on your computer. One of the ways we may use cookies is to identify computers that are being used to make visits to our Site. We also may customize, monitor, or regulate the use of our Site based on information stored in the cookie or host server. In addition, we use session cookies to recognize the user when moving from page to page in our Site. By using our Site, you consent to the use of our cookies.

 **3\. Release of Information**

We may disclose Personally Identifiable Information to our affiliates. We may also disclose Personally Identifiable Information to third parties that partner with us or provide services for us, and to other third parties as permitted by law. Currently, our disclosure of Personally Identifiable Information is limited to the following purposes: (i) understanding the use of our Site and making improvements; (ii) administering a mailing list for customers that have registered for such list; (iii) responding to requests from or providing any necessary notices to you; (iv) protecting the security or integrity of our Site; and (v) otherwise administering or managing our Site software.

We will encourage our service partners to adopt and post privacy policies. However, the use of your Personally Identifiable Information by our service partners is governed by the privacy policies of those service partners and is not subject to our control.

Occasionally, we may be required by law enforcement or judicial authorities to provide Personally Identifiable Information to the appropriate governmental authorities. We will disclose Personally Identifiable Information upon receipt of a court order or subpoena or to cooperate with a law enforcement investigation. We fully cooperate with law enforcement agencies in identifying those who use our services for illegal activities. We reserve the right to report to law enforcement agencies any activities that we in good faith believe to be unlawful.

We may also provide Non-Personally Identifiable Information about our customers' sales, traffic patterns, and related site information to third-party advertisers, but these statistics do not include any Personally Identifiable Information.

 **4\. Updating and Correcting Information**

You can access and modify certain personal information stored on our Site, such as your name, phone number, email address, and mailing address, by contacting us via email.

We retain information provided to us indefinitely unless otherwise stated. In addition, we will keep some personal information you have asked us to remove for the following purposes: (i) troubleshoot problems; (ii) assist with investigations; (iii) enforce our Site rules; or (iv) comply with legal requirements

Therefore, you should not expect that all of your Personally Identifiable Information will always be completely removed from our databases in response to your requests.

 **5\. User Choices on Collection and Use of Information**

We may, from time to time, send you e-mail regarding our products and services. In addition, if you signed up for our mailing list, we may occasionally send you direct mail about products and services that we feel may be of interest to you. Only Shoptalk (or agents working on behalf of Shoptalk) will send you these direct mailings and only if you indicated that you do not object to these offers. If you do not want to receive such e-mails or mailings, simply tell us when you give us your personal information. Or, at any time, you can modify your account information to no longer receive such offers and mailings.

You also have choices with respect to cookies. By modifying your browser preferences, you have the choice to accept all cookies, to be notified when a cookie is set, or to reject all cookies. If you choose to reject all cookies, some parts of our Site may not work properly.

 **6\. Security of Information**

We believe that keeping Personally Identifiable Information secure is one of our most significant responsibilities. We restrict access to Personally Identifiable Information about you to those employees and others who need to know that information to assist us in our business or to provide products or services to you. We safeguard Personally Identifiable Information according to established security standards and procedures, by maintaining physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards for the information.

Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your Personally Identifiable Information, you acknowledge that: (a) there are security and privacy limitations of the Internet which are beyond our control; (b) the security, integrity, and privacy of any and all information and data exchanged between you and us through our Site cannot be guaranteed; and (c) any such information and data may be viewed or tampered with in transit by a third party.

 **7\. Privacy Policies of Third-Party Websites**

When you use a link to go from our Site to a website operated by a third party, this General Privacy Policy is no longer in effect. We are not responsible for the privacy practices employed by third-party websites linked to or from our Site, nor for the information or content contained therein.

 **8\. Links to Other Websites**

We may provide links to other websites for your convenience and information. These sites operate independently from our Site and are not under our control. These sites may have their own privacy notices in place, which we strongly suggest you review if you visit any linked websites. We are not responsible for the content of these sites, any products or services that may be offered through these sites, or any other use of these sites.

 **HOW TO CONTACT US**

If you have any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy, or if you would like us to update certain information you have provided to us or your communication preferences, contact us by:

E-mailing us at: info@shoptalk.com  
Writing us at:  
Shoptalk, LLC  
622 Third Avenue, 35th Floor, New York, NY 10017

*****
